Register of the Herbert Hoover papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- New Deal Subject File, 1932-1960
  - Ideology (general), 1935-1936 (Box-folder 98: 6)
    Notes, pamphlets, printed articles, clippings, and circulated documents, 1932-1936, relating to competing political and economic systems. Includes Are Revolutions Necessary?; Downfall of Russia; Preserving the American Way of Giving; A Rising or a Setting Sun?; Roosevelt Warming the Serpent; A Statistical Survey of Public Opinion Regarding Current Economic and Social Problems; What, If Not Capitalism?
  - Illinois Conference on Social Welfare, 1935 (Box-folder 98: 7)
    Contains pamphlet titled, Shaping the Social Conscience of Illinois.
  - Jews and New Deal, clippings, 1938 (Box-folder 98: 8)
  - Joint Conference for Business Recovery, printed report, 1934 (Box-folder 98: 9)
  - Legislative process, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 98: 10)
    Notes, clippings, and typed excerpts from printed sources.
  - National Recovery Administration, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 98: 11)
    Notes, clippings, printed articles, National Recovery Administration and other governmental press releases, and typed excerpts from printed sources.
  - Prohibition repeal, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 98: 12)
  - Propaganda, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 98: 13)
  - Public works, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 99: 1)
    Notes, clippings, Federal Emergency Administration press releases, and typed excerpts from printed sources.
  - Reconstruction Finance Corporation, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 99: 2)
    Notes, clippings, Reconstruction Finance Corporation press releases, and typed excerpts from printed sources.
  - Revolution-Analogies with New Deal, clippings, 1937-1954 (Box-folder 99: 3)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D., 1936-1960 (Box-folder 99: 4)
    Typed excerpts from speeches by Roosevelt, and clipping.
  - Socialism-Analogies with New Deal, 1932-1936 (Box-folder 99: 5)
    Notes, clippings, printed articles, and pamphlet, Roads Back to Governmental Slavery.
  - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1933-1959 (Box-folder 99: 6)
    Notes, clippings, printed article, and Tennessee Valley Authority press releases.
  - Thatcher, Myron William, 1940 (Box-folder 99: 7)
    Pamphlet regarding associate of Henry A. Wallace, Why? A Story of Shocking Facts and of Abortive Efforts to Suppress Them.
- Communist Subversion Subject File, 1935-1965
  Drafts of writings, notes, memoranda, printed matter, and card files, used as research material for unpublished writings on communist subversion in the United States. Includes material collected for Hoover by Madeline Kelly
  - Bentley, Elizabeth, news dispatches, 1953 (Box-folder 99: 8)
  - Bridges, Harry, 1939-1952 (Box-folder 99: 9)
    Memorandum, clippings, and trial examiner report.
  - Browder, Earl, clippings, 1939-1957 (Box-folder 99: 10)
  - Bunche, Ralph, 1954 (Box-folder 99: 11)
    Clipping and report by Archibald Roosevelt.
  - Communism-United States (general)
    - Clippings, 1940-1965 (Box-folder 99: 12)
    - Clippings (contd.), 1940-1965 (Box-folder 100: 1-2)
    - Serial issues (assorted anti-communist journals), 1935-1962 (Box-folder 100: 3-4)
    - Pamphlets, 1938-1961 (Box-folder 101: 1-3)
      Includes A Business Man Looks at Communism; The Chickens of the Interventionist Liberals Have Come Home to Roost; Constitution of the Communist Party; Diplomacy and the Communist Challenge; Minutes of a Communist Cell on Art; Odyssey of a Fellow Traveler; Petition to the United States Congress to Investigate Treasonable Activities?; Socialist Reconstruction of Society; USA and USSR: The Economic Race; Understanding the Communists; What Is Socialism?
    - Miscellany, 1940-1961 (Box-folder 101: 4-5)
      Notes, memoranda, typed excerpts from printed sources, circulated documents, printed articles, and legislative bills.
  - Congress of Industrial Organizations
    - General, 1937-1961 (Box-folder 102: 1)
      Notes, memoranda, typed excerpts from printed sources, circulated documents, pamphlets, and other printed matter. Includes Communism and American Labor; The Hell of Herrin Rages Again.
    - Clippings, 1944-1957 (Box-folder 102: 2-5)
      Mainly regarding the Congress of Industrial Organizations Political Action Committee and especially its activities in the 1944 elections.
  - Espionage, 1948-1961 (Box-folder 103: 1)
    Notes, typed excerpts from printed sources, clippings, and congressional reports. Includes Exposé of Soviet Espionage, May 1960; Report on Soviet Espionage Activities in Connection with the Atom Bomb; Soviet Espionage through Poland.
  - Fair Play for Cuba Committee, 1963 (Box-folder 103: 2)
    Scope ant Contents note
    Congressional report, "Castro's Network in the United States."
  - Foundations, 1948-1954 (Box-folder 103: 3)
    Notes, memoranda, clippings, and other printed matter.
  - Freedom House
    - Freedom House issuances, 1941-1946 (Box-folder 103: 4-5)
      Flyers, leaflets, pamphlets, circulated documents, press releases, speeches, and radio broadcast transcripts. Includes The Faith of an American; The Negro's War; The Truth is Good News; What Does the War Mean to You?; World-wide Civil War.
    - Freedom House issuances (contd.) (Box-folder 104: 1)
    - Material about Freedom House, 1940-1947 (Box-folder 104: 2)
      Notes, memoranda, clippings, congressional record excerpts, and congressional reports and exhibits. Includes Investigation of Un-American Propaganda Activities in the United States; Special Report on Subversive Activities Aimed at Destroying Our Representative Form of Government.
  - Hiss, Alger, 1949-1962 (Box-folder 104: 3)
    Clippings and printed articles.
  - Institute of Pacific Relations, 1946-1960 (Box-folder 104: 4)
    Notes, memoranda, clippings, printed articles, and congressional report.
  - Lattimore, Owen, 1946-1955 (Box-folder 104: 5)
    Memorandum, clippings, printed articles, and circulated documents.
  - McCarthy, Joseph R., 1951-1957 (Box-folder 104: 6)
    Clippings, printed articles, radio broadcast transcripts, and congressional censure report. Includes printed copy of McCarthyism: The Fight for America, signed by McCarthy and inscribed to Hoover.
  - Oppenheimer, J. Robert, 1954-1956 (Box-folder 105: 1)
    Clippings, Atomic Energy Commission Personnel Security Board report, and associated documentation.
  - Organizations
    - Drafts of writings with lists of subversive organizations, and associated notes and memoranda, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 105: 2-4)
    - Printed matter, 1951-1961 (Box-folder 105: 5)
      Attorney General's list of subversive organizations, Congressional Guide to Subversive Organizations and Publications, and associated clippings and other printed matter.
    - Printed matter (contd.) (Box-folder 106: 1)
  - Pace, John T.--Testimony re Communist influence in 1932 Bonus March, 1938-1963 (Box-folder 106: 2)
    Printed transcript, memoranda, clippings, and other printed sources.
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.- Knowledge of Communist activities, 1938-1956 (Box-folder 106: 3)
    Memorandum, clippings, printed articles, typed excerpts from printed sources, and pamphlet The President Knows!
  - United Nations, 1953-1955 (Box-folder 106: 4)
    Clippings, serial issue, and pamphlet The United Nations and Communism.
  - United States, Army-Communist infiltration, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 106: 5)
  - United States, Congress, House, Committee on Un-American Activities, 1938-1961 (Box-folder 106: 6)
    Excerpts from committee reports and Congressional Record speeches, clippings, other printed matter, and circulated documents. Includes Committee Rules of Procedure.
  - United States, Congress, Senate, Committee on Education and Labor, 1950 (Box-folder 106: 7)
    Contains circulated report "The LaFollette Committee Unmasked."
  - United States, Congress, Senate, Committee on the Judiciary, Subcommittee on Internal Security, 1954-1957 (Box-folder 106: 8)
    Contains committee press releases.
  - United States, Department of State-Communist infiltration, 1947-1964 (Box-folder 106: 9)
    Memoranda, clippings, printed articles, Congressional Record speeches, congressional report, and pamphlets.
  - United States, Department of State-Communist infiltration (contd.) (Box-folder 107: 1)
  - United States, Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1946-1963 (Box-folder 107: 2)
    Bureau reports and press releases, speeches and printed articles by J. Edgar Hoover, and clippings.
  - United States government (general) - Communist infiltration
    - Drafts of writings with memoranda, notes, and typed excerpts from printed sources, 1950-1959 (Box-folder 107: 3)
    - Printed matter, 1947-1963 (Box-folder 107: 4)
    - Individuals, 1949-1950 and undated (Box-folder 107: 5)
      Drafts of writings with memoranda.
  - Waldrop, Frank C., 1950 (Box-folder 107: 6)
    Congressional Record reprints of articles by Waldrop.
  - White, Harry Dexter, 1953-1955 (Box-folder 107: 7)
    Notes, memoranda, clippings, printed articles, press releases, and Federal Bureau of Investigation report.
  - Card files
    - Subversive individuals (Box 108)
    - Subversive organizations (Boxes 109-110)
- World War II Subject File, 1918-1963
  Drafts of writings, notes, memoranda, letters, printed matter, and typed excerpts from printed sources, used as research material for unpublished writings on World War II. Includes material collected for Hoover by Arthur Kemp
  - Atom bomb, 1945-1947 (Box-folder 111: 1-2)
    Memorandum, clippings, printed articles, official report of Manhattan Project ( Atomic Energy for Military Purposes), and United States Strategic Bombing Survey reports ( Japan's Struggle to End the War; The Effects of Atomic Bombs on Hiroshima and Nagasaki; Summary Report: Pacific War.)
  - Balkans, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 111: 3)
    Clippings and press releases.
  - Baltic States, 1940-1946 (Box-folder 111: 4-5)
    Clippings, printed articles, serial issues, press releases, typed excerpts from printed sources, and pamphlets. Includes Lithuania in a Twin Teutonic Clutch; Lithuania under the Sickle and Hammer; Lithuania's Fight for Freedom.
  - Bulgaria, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 111: 6)
    Notes, clippings, printed excerpts, and typed excerpts from printed sources.
  - Byrnes, James F., 1943-1947 (Box-folder 111: 7-8)
    Clippings, printed speeches by Byrnes, and typed excerpts from Byrnes' memoirs and other printed sources.
  - China, 1938-1962 (Box-folder 112: 1)
    Draft writings, memoranda, clippings, printed articles, typed excerpts from printed sources, pamphlet ( Red Cloud over China), and letter by Patrick J. Hurley.
  - Chronology
    Drafts of writings, notes, memoranda, letters and typed transcripts of letters, speech transcripts, clippings, printed articles, pamphlets, and typed excerpts from printed sources
    - General (Box-folder 112: 2)
    - 1919-1936 (Box-folder 112: 3)
    - 1937 (Box-folder 112: 4)
    - 1938
      - "Diary" (actually chronology of world events and of activities by Hoover, prepared subsequently to their occurrence)
        - Concise version (Box-folder 112: 5)
        - Full version, including documentary inserts (Box-folder 112: 6)
        - Hoover visit to Europe, February-March (Box-folder 112: 7)
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 112: 8)
    - 1939
      - "Diary"
        - Concise version (Box-folder 112: 9)
        - Full version
          - January-June (Box-folder 113: 1)
          - July-September (Box-folder 113: 2)
          - October-December (Box-folder 113: 3)
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 113: 4)
    - 1940
      - "Diary"
        - Concise version
          - January-June (Box-folder 113: 5)
          - July-September (Box-folder 113: 6)
        - Full version
          - January-May (Box-folder 114: 1)
          - June-August (Box-folder 114: 2)
          - September (Box-folder 114: 3)
          - October (Box-folder 114: 4)
          - November-December (Box-folder 114: 5)
      - John C. O'Laughlin letters to Hoover (Box-folder 115: 1)
        Typed transcripts
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 115: 2)
    - 1941
      - "Diary"
        - Concise version
          - January-June (Box-folder 115: 3)
          - July-December (Box-folder 115: 4)
        - Full version
          - January-February (Box-folder 115: 5)
          - March-April (Box-folder 116: 1)
          - May-June (Box-folder 116: 2)
          - July-August (Box-folder 116: 3)
          - September (Box-folder 116: 4)
          - October (Box-folder 116: 4)
          - November (Box-folder 117: 1)
          - December 1-7 (Box-folder 117: 2)
          - December 8-31 (Box-folder 117: 3)
      - John C. O'Laughlin letters to Hoover (Box-folder 117: 4)
      - Miscellaneous drafts of writings, notes, and memoranda (Box-folder 117: 5)
      - Miscellaneous clippings (Box-folder 117: 6)
      - Miscellaneous clippings (contd.) (Box-folder 118: 1)
    - 1942
      - January-February (Box-folder 118: 2)
      - March-June (Box-folder 118: 3)
      - July-December (Box-folder 118: 4)
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 118: 5)
        Includes pamphlet Native Nazi Purge Plot
    - 1943
      - January-July (Box-folder 119: 1)
      - July-August (Box-folder 119: 2)
      - September-October (Box-folder 119: 3)
      - November-December (Box-folder 119: 4)
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 120: 1)
    - 1944
      - January-June (Box-folder 120: 2)
      - July-December (Box-folder 120: 3)
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 120: 4)
    - 1945
      - January-May (Box-folder 120: 5)
      - June-September (Box-folder 121: 1)
      - Miscellany (Box-folder 121: 2)
  - Churchill, Winston
    - Speech transcripts, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 121: 3)
    - Printed excerpts from memoirs, 1948-1953 (Box-folder 121: 4)
  - Conferences
    Drafts of writings, notes, memoranda, press releases and texts of conference statements, clippings, printed articles, pamphlets, printed excerpts, and typed excerpts from printed sources
    - Atlantic Charter Conference, 1941 August (Box-folder 122: 1)
      Includes booklet The Atlantic Charter and Africa from an American Viewpoint
    - Casablanca Conference, 1943 January (Box-folder 122: 2)
    - First Quebec Conference, 1943 August (Box-folder 122: 3)
    - Moscow Conference, 1943 October (Box-folder 122: 4)
      Includes printed report by Cordell Hull
    - First Cairo Conference, 1943 November (Box-folder 122: 5)
    - Tehran Conference, 1943 November-December (Box-folder 122: 6)
    - Second Cairo Conference, 1943 December (Box-folder 122: 7)
    - Second Quebec Conference, 1944 September (Box-folder 122: 8)
    - Malta Conference, 1945 January-February (Box-folder 122: 9)
    - Yalta Conference, 1945 February
      - Drafts of writings, notes, memoranda, and typed excerpts from printed sources (Box-folder 123: 1-2)
      - Printed matter (Box-folder 123: 3)
    - Potsdam Conference, 1945 July-August (Box-folder 123: 4)
      Includes pamphlet Potsdam or Peace
  - Czechoslovakia, 1938-1949 (Box-folder 123: 5)
  - Farley, James A., 1948 (Box-folder 123: 6)
    Typed excerpts from memoirs.
  - Finland, 1939-1962 (Box-folder 124: 1)
    Memoranda, notes, letters, clippings, printed excerpts, and typed excerpts from printed sources.
  - France, 1940-1945 (Box-folder 124: 2-3)
    Letter and report by René de Chambrun, and clippings.
  - Garner, John Nance, 1948 (Box-folder 124: 4)
    Printed and typed excerpts from memoirs.
  - Germany
    - General, 1934-1963 (Box-folder 124: 5)
      Drafts of writings, notes, memoranda, letters, reports, clippings, pamphlets, printed excerpts, and typed excerpts from printed sources. Includes The German White Paper; Hitlerism: Why and Whither.
    - Documents on German Foreign Policy, 1918-1945, 1956 (Box-folder 124: 6)
  - Great Britain, 1938-1962 (Box-folder 125: 1-2)
    Memoranda, notes, clippings, printed excerpts, and typed excerpts from printed sources.
  - Hopkins, Harry, 1948 (Box-folder 125: 3)
    Printed excerpts from biography by Robert E. Sherwood.
  - Hull, Cordell, 1948 (Box-folder 125: 4)
    Printed excerpts from memoirs.
  - Ickes, Harold L., 1948 (Box-folder 125: 5)
  - Italy, 1945-1949 (Box-folder 125: 6)
    Memoranda, printed article, and printed excerpts.
  - Japan
    - Draft writings and typed excerpts from printed sources (Box-folder 125: 7)
    - Letters and memoranda, 1934-1963 (Box-folder 126: 1)
    - Clippings, printed articles, and printed excerpts, 1941-1962 (Box-folder 126: 2)
      Includes U.S. Department of State Bulletin re Pearl Harbor attack
    - Typed excerpts from memoirs of Prince Fumimaro Konoye with associated notes and clippings, 1945 (Box-folder 126: 3)
  - Kennedy, Joseph P., clippings, 1940-1962 (Box-folder 126: 4)
  - MacArthur, Douglas, 1943-1953 (Box-folder 126: 5)
    Photocopies of MacArthur-Hoover correspondence, typed transcript of MacArthur letter to Bonner Fellers, and typed transcript of news story.
  - Marshall, George C., 1945-1963 (Box-folder 126: 6)
    Clippings, printed articles, and printed report by Marshall, The Winning of the War in Europe and the Pacific.
  - Morgenthau, Henry, Jr., and Morgenthau Plan, 1944-1948 (Box-folder 126: 7)
    Printed excerpts from Morgenthau diaries, clippings, printed articles, memoranda, and notes.
  - Neutrality--United States
    - General, 1941-1962 (Box-folder 126: 8)
      Letter by Hoover, memoranda, notes, clippings, Congressional Record speeches, and typed excerpts from printed sources.
    - Anti-intervention issuances, circa 1939-1941 (Box-folder 126: 9)
      Circulated documents and leaflets. Includes pamphlet Anti-War Crusade.
    - Pro-intervention issuances, 1939-1941 (Box-folder 126: 10)
      Circulated documents and leaflets. Includes Fight for Freedom pamphlet It's Fun to Be Free.
    - John Venuti (crew member, U.S.S. Orizaba) log of U.S. Navy operations in the Atlantic with ship newsletter issues, 1941 (Box-folder 126: 11)
  - O'Laughlin, John C., 1939-1941 (Box-folder 127: 1)
    Photocopies and typed transcripts of O'Laughlin-Hoover correspondence.
  - Poland
    Drafts of writings, notes, memoranda, clippings, printed excerpts, and typed excerpts from printed sources.
    - General (Box-folder 127: 2)
    - 1939-1941 (Box-folder 127: 3)
    - 1942-1943 (Box-folder 127: 4)
    - 1944 (Box-folder 127: 5)
    - 1945 (Box-folder 127: 6)
    - Polish Government-in-Exile pamphlets, 1943-1946 (Box-folder 127: 7-8)
      Includes Poland Accuses; Polish-Soviet Relations, 1918-1943; Polish Facts and Figures series
    - Polish-American organization issuances, 1942-1946 (Box-folder 128: 1)
      Resolutions, petitions, pamphlets, and transcripts of letters. Includes An Appeal to Franklin Delano Roosevelt...on Behalf of Poland; The Case for Poland; Great Britain's Obligations towards Poland.
    - Katyn Forest Massacre, 1945-1949 (Box-folder 128: 2)
      Clippings and pamphlet Death at Katyn.
  - Postwar planning, memorandum and clipping, 1943 (Box-folder 128: 3)
  - Romania, clippings, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 128: 4)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.
    - General, 1942-1949 (Box-folder 128: 5)
      Memoranda, clippings, and printed articles. Includes printed compendium of speeches by Roosevelt from 1933 to 1942, Development of United States Foreign Policy.
    - Speech transcripts on foreign policy
      Printed texts and printed and typed excerpts
      - 1935-1938 (Box-folder 128: 6)
      - 1939 (Box-folder 128: 7-8)
      - 1940 (Box-folder 129: 1-2)
      - 1941 (Box-folder 129: 3)
      - 1943 (Box-folder 129: 4)
  - Soviet Union
    Memoranda, notes, clippings, printed articles, and printed and typed excerpts
    - General (Box-folder 130: 1)
    - 1918-1940 (Box-folder 130: 2)
    - 1941 (Box-folder 130: 3)
    - 1942 (Box-folder 130: 4)
    - 1943 (Box-folder 130: 5)
    - 1944 (Box-folder 130: 6)
    - 1945 (Box-folder 130: 7)
  - Spain, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 130: 8)
    Memorandum, clippings, and press releases of the Spanish Embassy in the United States.
  - Stettinius, Edward R., Jr., 1943-1946 (Box-folder 130: 9)
    Clippings, speech transcripts, and printed excerpt.
  - Stilwell, Joseph, 1948-1956 (Box-folder 130: 10)
    Printed article and printed excerpts.
  - Stimson, Henry L., 1948 (Box-folder 130: 11)
  - Truman, Harry S., 1944-1945 (Box-folder 131: 1-2)
    Clippings and speech transcripts.
  - Yugoslavia, circa 1943-1945 (Box-folder 131: 3)
    Clippings, and pamphlets. Includes The Political Situation in Yugoslavia Today; Shall Slovenia Be Sovietized?
  - Miscellany notes, undated (Box-folder 131: 4)
- General Subject File, 1918-1965
  Drafts of writings, notes, memoranda, letters, printed matter, and typed excerpts from printed sources, mainly relating to the post-World War II period and in part used as research material for unpublished writings. Includes material collected for Hoover by Arthur Kemp
  - Africa, clippings, 1952-1961 (Box-folder 132: 1)
  - Aged, 1959 (Box-folder 132: 2)
    Congressional Report, The Aged and the Aging in the United States.
  - Americanism, 1933-1959 (Box-folder 132: 3)
    Notes, clippings, printed articles, serial issues, essays, speeches, typed excerpts from printed sources, and circulated documents.
  - Asia, 1951-1964 (Box-folder 132: 4)
    Notes, clippings, and report by Claude A. Buss.
  - Austria, 1945-1946 (Box-folder 132: 5)
    Clippings, printed article, and report by Frank E. Mason.
  - Balkans, clippings, 1946-1953 (Box-folder 132: 6)
  - Belgian American Educational Foundation, Report and Directory of Fellows for the Years 1952-1957 (Box-folder 132: 7)
  - Bulgaria, notes and clippings, 1945-1948 (Box-folder 132: 8)
  - Bullitt, William C., 1935-1948 (Box-folder 132: 9)
    Clippings, printed articles, and printed dispatches from Moscow.
  - Byrnes, James F., 1946-1950 (Box-folder 132: 10)
    Clippings, printed article, and printed speeches.
  - Byrnes, James F. (contd.) (Box-folder 133: 1)
  - China
    - Drafts of writings, with memoranda, notes, and circulated material, 1945-1964 (Box-folder 133: 2)
    - Clippings, printed articles, and printed excerpts from the Congressional Record and other sources, 1945-1962 (Box-folder 133: 3-4)
    - Pamphlets and congressional reports, 1949-1963 (Box-folder 133: 5)
      Includes Bishop Walsh of Maryknoll; China: Key to the Orient and to Asia; China Lob-Lolly; The Committee of One Million; Communist China: A Nation Enslaved; Testimony of a Defector from Communist China
    - Pamphlets and congressional reports (contd.), 1949-1963 (Box-folder 134: 1)
  - Chronology
    Drafts of writings, notes, memoranda, speeches, typed excerpts from printed sources, press releases, clippings, and printed articles
    - 1945 October-December (Box-folder 134: 2)
    - 1946 (Box-folder 134: 3)
    - 1947 (Box-folder 134: 4)
    - 1948 (Box-folder 134: 5)
    - 1949-1950 (Box-folder 134: 6)
    - 1951 (Box-folder 134: 7-8)
    - 1952-1963 (Box-folder 135: 1)
  - Churchill, Winston, printed article re Boer War experiences, 1963 (Box-folder 135: 2)
  - Communism
    - General, 1954-1961 (Box-folder 135: 3)
      Clippings, printed articles, typed excerpts from printed sources, speeches, and Congressional Reports.
    - Problems of Communism, serial issues, 1958-1964 (Box-folder 135: 4-5)
  - Conferences
    Clippings, printed articles, and communiqués
    - Three-Power Conference, Moscow, 1945 December (Box-folder 136: 1)
    - Council of Foreign Ministers, Paris, 1946 April-July, 1945 December (Box-folder 136: 2-4)
    - Peace Conference, Paris, 1946 July-October (Box-folder 137: 1-4)
    - Council of Foreign Ministers, New York City, 1946 November-December (Box-folder 138: 1-2)
    - Council of Foreign Ministers, London, 1947 January-February (Box-folder 138: 3)
    - Council of Foreign Ministers, Moscow, 1947 March-April (Box-folder 138: 4)
    - Council of Foreign Ministers, Moscow (contd.), 1947 March-April (Box-folder 139: 1-2)